What's so funny?
你在笑什麼？
Nothing. It's an acting exercise. I'm practicing my fake laugh.
沒有，這是演技練習 我在練假笑
What? What's so funny?
你在笑什麼？
No,no. There's none of that in here.
不行，店裡不准抽煙
Come on. At least let me finish this last one.
至少讓我抽完這一根
Only if you give me a drag.
好，但你得分我一口
Oh,dark mother,once again I suckle at your smoky teat.
妖女，我又吻上你的唇了
Why don't you hold on to that one.
整根都給你吧
That's like the least fun game ever.
這是最不好玩的遊戲
I'm sick of your smoking, so I brought something...
我受夠了，我帶了一樣東西
...that is going to help you quit.
可以幫助你戒煙
That patch is no good.
這個戒煙帖布不好用
It's a hypnosis tape.
這是催眠錄音帶
A woman at work used it for two weeks and hasn't smoked since.
我一個同事聽了 兩星期後再也沒抽過煙
What's your problem?
你有什麼意見？
Nothing. It's just that hypnosis is beyond crap.
沒什麼，只不過催眠是騙人的
I watched you get hypnotized in Atlantic City.
我在亞特蘭大看過你被催眠
That guy did not hypnotize me,okay?
那傢伙沒把我催眠，好嗎？
You always pull your pants down and play "Wipe Out" on your butt.
是啊，你總是脫褲子 用屁股「通殺」
Forget hypnosis.
別用催眠了
The way to quit smoking is to dance naked in a field of heather...
想戒煙就得去石南地上裸舞
...and then bathe in the sweat of six healthy,young men.
然後用六個壯丁的汗水沐浴
Or what my father calls "Thursday night."
我爸管它叫「週四夜狂歡」
The One With the Hypnosis Tape
本集播出：「老少配」
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河馬壓縮製作 本字幕為河馬根據R3DVD OCR得來
-Here you go. -I didn't want cinnamon on this.
拿去 我不要加肉桂
Sorry.
對不起
Oh,my God! Frank!
天哪，法蘭克
How are you?
你好嗎？
What are you doing here?
你怎麼來了？
I would've called, but I lost your number.
我本來想先打電話 但是號碼弄丟了
And then my mom locked me out of the house,so I couldn't find it.
我媽把我鎖在門外 我沒辦法進去找
Then I tried to find a pay phone, and the receiver was cut off.
我找了一具公共電話 話筒卻被剪斷了
What happened?
怎麼了？
Vandalism.
有人破壞公物
But also,what happened between you and your mom?
那你和你媽怎麼了？
We got in a fight. She said that I was too immature to get married.
我們吵架，她說我 不夠成熟，不能結婚
You're getting married?
你要結婚了？
My little brother's getting married!
我的弟弟要結婚了
I knew you'd be so cool about this. Do you wanna meet her?
我就知道你會替我高興 你想見她嗎？
Do l?
你說呢？
Do you?
你想嗎？
Yeah,I do.
當然想
Cool,all right. She's just parking the truck.
太好了，她正在停卡車
I gonna go get my fiancee,man!
我去帶我的未婚妻來
I'd have bet good money that he'd be the first one of us to get married.
我就知道他會最早結婚
Isn't it fantastic?
這不是很棒嗎？
Don't you think he's a little young to get married?
你不覺得他稍嫌年輕？
Well,he's 18.
他已經18歲了
It'll be illegal for him to drink at his own bachelor party.
他在最後單身派對上不能喝酒
Yeah,or to get a hooker.
也不能叫雞
Always illegal,Joe.
叫雞本來就違法
This is my fiancee...
這是我的未婚妻
... Mrs. IKnight.
奈特老師
That's my sister.
那是我姐姐
You know,it's funny.
說來好笑
Frank told me so much about you,but you're not how I pictured you at all.
法蘭克經常提到你 你卻跟我想像的不一樣
Yeah,I'm a big surprise.
是啊，我很令人意外
Here,grab a seat.
坐吧
So how did you guys meet?
你們是怎麼認識的？
I was in Mrs. IKnight's....
我去上奈特老師的…
I mean,Alice. Sorry. I always do that.
我是說愛麗絲 抱歉，我老是叫錯
I was in her home-ec class.
我去上她的家政課
He was my best student.
他是我最好的學生
She was my best teacher.
她是我最好的老師
If that doesn't keep kids in school, what will?
真是讓學生不蹺課的好方法
And so now you guys are gonna be married?
你們要結婚了？
We talked about just living together...
我們本來只考慮同居
...but we want kids right away.
但是我們想馬上生小孩
Oh,my God!
天哪
Great!
太好了
IKids. Frank,are you sure you're ready for that?
小孩？法蘭克 你真的準備好了？
How hard can it be?
能有多難？
You know,I mean,babies. Who doesn't want babies? Right?
誰不想要小寶寶，對吧？
And besides, I never had a dad around.
而且我一直沒有爸爸陪伴
And now I always will, because it'll be me.
以後就有了，因為我就是爸爸
Really,we do realize that there's an age difference between us.
我們知道我們的歲數差很多
Good. Because you were acting like you didn't.
那就好 你們看起來好像不知道
But when it comes to love, what does age matter?
但是在愛情裡，年齡不是問題
You are falling fast asleep.
你正在進入夢鄉
Deeper,deeper,deeper.
越睡越沉，越睡越沉
You are now completely asleep.
你已經睡著了
You don't need to smoke.
你不需要抽煙
Cigarettes don't control you.
香煙不能控制你
You are a strong,confident woman...
你是堅強、有自信的女性
... who does not need to smoke.
你不需要抽煙
A strong,confident woman.
堅強、有自信的女性
You know what?
你知道嗎？
I realized in the last year I've only gone out with Richard and Julio.
我發現去年我只和 李察、胡立歐交往過
You gotta help me out,set me up. Get me back in the game.
你得幫我牽線，讓我重回情場
Not a problem.
沒問題
I work in fashion,and all I meet are eligible straight men.
我在時裝界工作 身邊全是異性戀好男人
Can I get you something else?
你還要什麼？
Cheesecake and a date, if you're giving them out.
起司蛋糕 和一次約會，如果有的話
Haven't we covered that topic?
我們不是談過了嗎？
You just said to her
你剛才對她說…
You wanna go out with me...
你想跟我約會
... because of my wig,the big boobs, and I serve you food.
是因為我是金髮、波霸 還端吃的給你
If that were true, I'd be dating my Aunt Ruth.
那我找我姑姑就行了
And the two times we went out, it was plain awkward.
我們一起出門兩次，都蠻慘的
You think she should go out with me, don't you?
你覺得她應該和我約會吧？
You sure you wanna go out with her?
你真的想跟她約會？
That ain't a pretty picture in the morning.
早上會慘不忍睹喔
That wig all in disarray, and boobs flung over the nightstand.
假髮亂成一團 義乳扔在床頭櫃上
Think about it.
你考慮一下
Oh,I will.
我會的
No,I know. I know that this is Frank's life.
我知道這是法蘭克的人生
I don't wanna be judgmental, but it's sick. It's sick and wrong!
我不想批評 但這樣是變態、是錯的
What,is it the age thing?
因為年齡的關係？
I'm fine with the age thing...
我本來不在乎年齡
...until it sticks its tongue down my brother's throat.
直到她把舌頭往我弟的喉嚨伸
Pheebs,he seems to enjoy it.
菲比，他看起來很爽
You think he'll enjoy it when he's up to his elbows in diapers...
等他忙著幫一堆寶寶換尿布
...of all the babies they have to have right away?
你覺得他還會爽嗎？
This is not fair to Frank, and it's not fair to the babies.
這樣對法蘭克不公平 也對寶寶不公平
You know what? It's not good home economics.
這可不是好的家政
Have you told him how you feel?
你跟他說過嗎？
Yes. Not out loud.
有，但沒有說出聲音
If you don't tell him,soon he'll be married,then you'll hate yourself.
你不說，他就要結婚了 你會恨你自己
Yeah,but if I do tell him, then he's gonna hate myself.
我要是說了，他會恨我
Look at him and his mom. I can't.
你看看他和他媽媽，我不能說
But you guys can. You talk him out of it.
但是你們可以，你們去勸阻他
Come on,you guys.
拜託啦
You have nothing to lose. I have everything to lose.
你們沒有損失 我卻會失去一切
Do you want me to lose everything? Everything?
你們要我失去一切嗎？
Okay,I'm gonna go get Frank.
好，我去找法蘭克
We're walking down the street, and I turn to you and say:
剛才走在街上，我對你說
"Let's go hang out at Totally Nude Nudes." Remember?
「去脫衣酒吧坐坐」 記得嗎？
And then you say,"Let's just hang out at your place."
然後你說「去你家就好了」
Well,that was a nice move,dumb ass.
好明智啊，豬頭
I think you should go out with this guy.
你應該跟他約會
He doesn't do anything for me.
他對我一點吸引力也沒有
Last Saturday night,what happened on Walker,Texas Ranger?
上週六的 「猛龍過江」演什麼？
Walker was looking for this big busload of kids.
沃克在找一車子的小孩…
All right,I get your point.
我懂你的意思了
I forgot the combination to this about a year ago.
我一年前就忘了它的密碼
I just carry it around.
我只是拎著裝樣子
You got any Chap Stick?
你們有護唇膏嗎？
How are those tapes working out?
錄音帶聽得怎樣？
Good. I haven't smoked yet today.
很有效，我今天還沒抽煙
I feel great and confident. That is a stunning blouse.
清爽又有自信 好漂亮的上衣
Thank you.
謝謝
-Here you go. -Thanks.
拿去 謝了
Let's give Pete a chance. He was funny. He seems really nice.
給彼特一個機會 他既風趣，人又好
That check thing was adorable.
而且支票的事好可愛
What check thing?
什麼支票？
As a joke,this customer who has a crush on me,gave me a $20,000 tip.
有個喜歡我的顧客開玩笑 給我兩萬元的小費
His number's on the check. He did it so I'd call.
他的電話在支票上 他要我打給他
Pete Becker. Pete
彼特貝克，彼特…
Is this him?
是他嗎？
That's Bill Clinton.
那是總統
Who's he hugging?
他抱著誰？
Oh,my God. That's Pete. Why is Bill hugging Pete?
天哪，是彼特 總統為什麼抱著彼特？
This guy invented Moss 865.
他發明了摩斯865
Every office in the world uses that program.
全世界的公司都在用這個程式
-We use it! -There you go!
我們也在用 你看吧
Monica's gonna go out with a millionaire.
摩妮卡要跟百萬富翁約會了
I'm not gonna go out with him.
我才不跟他約會
I can't believe this is a real $20,000 check. This is so exciting.
這居然是真的兩萬元支票 好興奮喔
Or incredibly offensive.
或是令人火大
Yeah,sure. That too.
對，也有
What?
怎樣？
All we're saying is, don't rush into anything.
我們的意思是，不要操之過急
Come on,think about it. You're 18. She's 44.
你想想：你18歲，她44歲
When you're 36,she's gonna be 88.
等你36歲，她就88歲了
You don't think I know that?
你以為我不知道？
The point is...
重點是…
...there's a lot of women you haven't had sex with yet.
你還可以跟很多女人上床
He's right. He's right. This is your time.
他說得對，這是你的天下
You're young. You're weird. Chicks dig that.
你年輕，你古怪 女生最喜歡了
Isn't sex better when it's with one person that you really care about?
跟一個你很喜歡的人做 感覺不是更棒？
Yeah,in a poem,maybe.
在詩裡吧
No,the man's right. That's what I had with Rachel.
不，他說得對 我跟瑞秋就是那樣
Not anymore?
現在沒有了？
No. I slept with someone else.
沒了，我跟別人上了床
So wait. So how did that make things better?
等等，那樣對事情有幫助嗎？
It didn't.
沒有
What you used to have with Rachel is what I got with Alice.
你跟瑞秋的感覺 就是我和愛麗絲的感覺
Now,what is that like?
那是什麼感覺？
It's so cool,man.
很棒的感覺
It's because being with her is so much better than not being with her.
因為跟她在一起 比不跟她在一起快樂多了
-Why can't I find that? -I had it and I blew it.
我為什麼找不到？ 我擁有過，卻搞砸了
Well,I want it!
我想要！
You can have it.
你一定可以擁有
Maybe there's something wrong with me.
也許我有毛病
No,it's out there,man. I've seen it! I got it!
你會找到的 我見過，也擁有了
-Then,you hold on to it! -All right,man!
那你就要好好把握 好
All right! Congratulations, you lucky bastard!
死小子，恭喜你
You're Frank's best man?
你是法蘭克的伴郎？
I couldn't help it. Their love is so pure.
我沒辦法，他們的愛好純潔
What about you,huh?
那你呢？
I'm the ring bearer.
我幫他拿戒指
I'm so glad you could come. I've got a real home-ec emergency.
你來了就好 我有一個家政慘案
Oh,my God. Who died on this?
天哪，誰死了？
It's a real "mustard-tastrophe."
芥末醬倒了
Can you help?
你有辦法嗎？
Absolutely. First,we'll start with a little club soda and salt.
當然有，先用蘇打水加鹽清洗
-Then if that doesn't work -Forget it. It's ruined.
要是洗不掉，就… 算了，它已經毀了
Never say that. If you can't get it out,cut around the stain...
別這麼說，要是洗不掉 就剪掉髒污部份
...add a little lace, you make a stylish throw.
縫一點蕾絲 就是一條漂亮的遮布
Or instead,maybe you could just not marry my brother,Frank?
又或者，你可以 不要嫁給我弟弟
Can we make it smaller? Make it fit on the head of a pin?
能不能讓它小到 可以放在針尖上？
I love when we make things fit on the head of a pin.
我喜歡生產這種小東西
You have Monica Geller here.
摩妮卡蓋勒來訪
Absolutely. Yeah,send her in.
好的，讓她進來
What the hell is this?
這是什麼意思？
Hang on for a sec. I'll talk to you in the morning?
等一下…明天早上再談？
You got it.
好的
I'm sorry. What?
對不起，什麼？
What's this supposed to mean?
這是什麼意思？
Well,you know, I never know how much to tip.
我一直不會算小費
You double the tax. Not double the tax of Romania.
把加稅乘以二 不是把羅馬尼亞的稅收乘以二
Are you buying me? Is this how you get girls to go out with you?
你要買我嗎？ 你都這樣約女孩子？
I'm still here.
我還在
You're taking this wrong. If I didn't leave you that tip...
你誤會了 要是我沒給這筆小費
...you wouldn't have come, we wouldn't have this argument...
你就不會來，我們不會爭吵
...and there wouldn't be this heat between us.
也不會有這種緊張的氣氛
You gotta admit that our relationship is hitting a new level now.
你得承認我們的關係有進展了
You were the chef and I was the customer.
以前你是廚師，我是顧客
But now we're this couple that fights.
現在我們是兩個爭吵的人
You're a loon.
你是個瘋子
Look,forget the check,okay? I like you.
別管這張支票了，我喜歡你
I think you're great.
我覺得你很棒
Come on,what do you say?
怎麼樣？
I don't know.
我不知道
Why not?
為什麼？
I don't wanna encourage this behavior.
我不想鼓勵這種行為
One meal. That's all I'm asking for. Please?
我只求一頓飯，好嗎？
We go out,we eat.
我們出去吃飯
If you don't have a good time, I'll give you 10 grand,we're even.
要是玩得不開心 我給你一萬，我們扯平
Wait,no. Just put the mail down. It's me.
不，把信放下，是我
Sorry. Why were you just all in the dark?
對不起，你怎麼不開燈？
Your laundry smelled so good that I thought I'd curl up in it.
你的衣服好香，我就窩在裡面
-ls that all right? -Yeah,sure.
沒關係吧？ 沒關係
So how was your day?
今天過得怎樣？
It's just probably the worst one since I've been alive.
可能是我有生以來最慘的一天
What happened?
怎麼了？
Alice.... She called it off.
愛麗絲改變心意了
Did she say why?
她有說原因嗎？
No. Just that I was too young.
沒有，她只說我太年輕
I don't see how I could suddenly be too young...
我怎麼突然變年輕了？
... because I'm older than I was when we first got together.
剛交往時，她還說我老成
I don't know. But you know what? Maybe it's just all for the best.
不曉得，但是你知道嗎？ 或許這樣也好
Well,yeah,if the best is like unbelievable pain.
是啊，但是我好痛苦
Oh,sweetie.
親愛的
You know,I was just finally happy.
我好不容易感到快樂
For the first time in my life...
這是生平第一次
...after my dad left me...
先是爸爸離開我…
...and then getting arrested for stealing those birds...
然後偷鳥被逮捕…
...and then the whole punctured-lung thing.
然後又肺穿孔
It's still really hard to take deep breaths in cold weather...
天氣一冷，我還是很難深呼吸
...but with Alice, all that stuff kind of went away.
但是有了愛麗絲 這些都不見了
And now it's gone, and I don't know why.
現在我失去了，卻不知道原因
Well,I can tell you why. It's because of me.
我可以告訴你，是我害的
But you know what? I only did it because I love you,okay?
不過我是愛你才這麼做
What?
什麼？
I kind of had a little chat with Alice...
我跟愛麗絲聊了一下
...and I sort of made her see why you two shouldn't be together.
讓她明白你們為何不能在一起
And you'll see it too,one day. You really,really will.
你總有一天也會明白，真的
Wait a minute. This is because of you?
等一下，是你造成的？
My mother didn't want us to be together...
我媽反對我們在一起
...but the worst thing she did was tie me to the porch.
但是她頂多把我綁在門廊上
I came to you because I thought you'd understand.
我覺得你能瞭解，所以來找你
I would storm out of here...
我很想摔門走人
...if I had some money or a place to go.
但是我沒錢、沒地方去
Oh,my God! The millionaire's here!
天哪，大富豪來了
Oh,my God!
天哪
I'm just gonna have dinner with him.
我只是要跟他吃頓飯
Okay,just because he buys you dinner does not mean you owe him anything.
他請你吃飯 並不代表你欠他什麼
I know.
我知道
Okay,then get the lobster.
那記得點龍蝦
How much cash you got in your pocket now?
你口袋裡有多少現金？
And that's why I'm not inviting you in for a drink.
我就不請你進來坐了
Why not? Hey,come in for drink.
進來坐一下嘛
-Where do you wanna go? -You like pizza?
你想去哪裡？ 喜歡吃披薩嗎？
-That sounds great. -I know a great little place.
聽起來不錯 有一家館子不錯
You're not paying for the pizza.
我不能讓你付錢
Come on,it's only fair. You paid for the flight.
這樣很公平，你出了機票錢
Is that enough lira?
這些里拉夠嗎？
I'd throw another 1000 on that.
再丟個一千
-How much is that? -That's about 60 cents.
這樣是多少？ 大約60毛美金
Every night!
每天晚上都這樣
You don't need to smoke.
你不需要抽煙
Cigarettes don't control you.
香煙不能控制你
You are a strong,confident woman...
你是堅強、有自信的女性
... who does not need to smoke.
你不需要抽煙
A strong,confident woman...
堅強、有自信的女性
... who does not need to smoke.
不需要抽煙
Look,I know that you think I did this totally evil thing.
我知道你覺得我做了大壞事
But I so didn't.
但是我沒有
Someone's here who can explain this better than I can.
有一個人可以解釋得比我清楚
Hi,Mrs. IKnight.
奈特老師
Phoebe's right,Frank.
法蘭克，菲比說得對
It's hard to hear,but it would've been wrong to go through with it.
這話不中聽，但我們不該結婚
I was being selfish.
我太自私了
Even though we want the same things right now...
我們現在追求相同的東西
...in the future,we may not.
未來卻不見得如此
-ls that what it is? -Yes,but not just that.
對不對？ 對，但不只如此
Not just that.
不只如此
Even though we love each other as much as we do...
雖然我們現在非常相愛
... nonetheless....
然而…
Nonetheless.
You're too young...
你還年輕…
...to really know what you want.
不曉得你要什麼
That's right,exactly.
沒錯
That's a goodbye kiss. That's good.
你們在吻別，很好
Bye-bye.
再見
The important thing is, is that you see what I'm saying.
總之希望你瞭解我的意思
This is clearly wrong.
這麼做擺明是錯的
I've decided I'm gonna let this happen.
我絕不會袖手旁觀
Can I just get my purse?
我要拿皮包
Okay,all right,good.
好吧，算了
Cigarettes don't control you.
香煙不能控制你
You are a strong,confident woman...
你是堅強、有自信的女性
... who does not need to smoke.
你不需要抽煙
Joey's your best friend.
喬伊是你最要好的朋友
You wanna make him a cheese sandwich every day.
你要每天為他做起司三明治
And you also wanna buy him hundreds of dollars worth of pants.
你還要送他一條幾百塊的褲子